

Queens, NY

□ (+1) 347-430-3398 | Schristianmsakai@gmail.com | Ochristiansakai | Christiansakai

Summary ____

Software Engineer with around 4 years of experience specializing in fullstack web development. Interests in web development, programming languages, compilers, systems development and software engineering best practices. Play guitar, bass and sing to keep myself creative, practice karate to keep myself healthy.

Skills

Proficient JavaScript/TypeScript, HTML & CSS, Express, React, Redux, NodeJS, MongoDB, Webpack, Grunt, Gulp, Git

Knowledgeable Rust, Elixir, Phoenix, Ecto, PostgreSQL, Sass, Haskell, LTFX

Basic C, C++, Java, Lisp, AWS, Docker, D3

Work Experience _____

ITN Networks New York City

FRONT END ENGINEER

Jul. 2018 - PRESENT

• Worked on various features on company's Provantagex web app

IrisVR Inc.

New York City

SOFTWARE ENGINEER CONSULTANT Oct. 2016 - Mar. 2018

- · Implemented build system on company's front end and desktop app development environment using Webpack
- Designed failure-point handling to handle disconnections between several NodeJS backend services gracefully
- Migrated company's MongoDB and AWS Redshift database changes with ensured consistency

FactorSpot Maryland

SOFTWARE ENGINEER CONSULTANT

VARIOUS CONTRACT DATES

- Designed security policy over company's Firebase data
- Built Bobtail fullstack web app

Ninthbeat Inc.

New York City

CO-FOUNDER & SOFTWARE ENGINEER Mar. 2015 - Dec. 2015

- Built company's web app using MEAN stack
- Built company's smartphone app using Ionic

Fullstack Academy

New York City

Jul. 2014 - Feb. 2015

Assisted instructors on lecture and reviewed student projects

- Designed a Grunt workshop for students
- Built company's internal social media platform web app

Education

TEACHING FELLOW

Queens College Flushing, NY

M.A. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE (3.9 GPA) 2016 - 2018

Alliance Theological Seminary Manhattan, NY

M.Div. in Theological Studies 2010 - 2013

Bina Nusantara University

Jakarta, Indonesia

B.Eng. in Industrial Engineering 2004 - 2008

DECEMBER 3, 2018 CHRISTIAN SAKAI · RÉSUMÉ